pqsofts.com 2011-05-27

# Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction

We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our [Terms of Use](http://www.joomshaper.com/terms-of-use).

### 2\. Types of information we collect

**Personal Data  
** This is data that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you and may include your name, address, email address, user IP addresses in circumstances where they have not been deleted, clipped or anonymised, and telephone number. Such information is only collected from you if you voluntarily submit it to us.

**Non-Personal Data  
** Like most websites, we gather statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website. This Non-Personal Data comprises information that cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information regarding, for example, user IP addresses where they have been clipped or anonymised, browser types and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our website.

### 3\. Use of data

No information submitted by a you will be shared, sold, reused in lists, or be used for any other purpose than to complete a transaction or address a customer service concern.

### 4\. Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings but we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### 5\. Children

We do not allow persons who are ages thirteen or younger to become members of this site. If your under age 13, do not use personal information with us.

### 6\. External links

When you click on a link on this web site that takes you to a web site operated by another company, you will be subjected to that company's web site privacy policies.

### 7\. Contact information

If you have any question about this policy or our site, please feel free to contact with us using **info(at)joomxpert.com** email address.

### 8\. Correcting/Updating personal information

You are free to update your information at any time directly through our Site. To change your information please log in at http://www.joomshaper.com and click on "Your Details" link
